http://www.lowtherloudspeakers.com/privacy-policy

TOWARDS PERFECTION
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. It is Lowther Loudspeaker Systems Ltd’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://lowtherloudspeakers.com, and other sites we own and operate.
1. Information we collect
Log data
When you visit our website, our servers may automatically
log the standard data provided by your web browser. It may include your
computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and version, the
pages you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on each page,
and other details.
Device data
We may also collect data about the device you’re using to
access our website. This data may include the device type, operating system,
unique device identifiers, device settings, and geo-location data. What we
collect can depend on the individual settings of your device and software. We
recommend checking the policies of your device manufacturer or software
provider to learn what information they make available to us.
Personal information
We may ask for personal information, such as your:
NameEmailPhone/mobile numberHome/Mailing address Work address Payment information
2. Legal bases for processing
We will process your personal information lawfully, fairly
and in a transparent manner. We collect and process information about you only
where we have legal bases for doing so.
These legal bases depend on the services you use and how you
use them, meaning we collect and use your information only where:
it’s necessary for the performance of a contract to which
you are a party or to take steps at your request before entering into such a
contract (for example, when we provide a service you request from us);
it satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden
by your data protection interests), such as for research and development, to
market and promote our services, and to protect our legal rights and interests;
you give us consent to do so for a specific purpose (for
example, you might consent to us sending you our newsletter); or
we need to process your data to comply with a legal
obligation.
Where you consent to our use of information about you for a
specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time (but this
will not affect any processing that has already taken place).
We don’t keep personal information for longer than is
necessary. While we retain this information, we will protect it within
commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as
unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. That said, we
advise that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure and
cannot guarantee absolute data security. If necessary, we may retain your
personal information for our compliance with a legal obligation or in order to
protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.
3. Collection and use of information
We may collect, hold, use and disclose information for the
following purposes and personal information will not be further processed in a
manner that is incompatible with these purposes:
to contact and communicate with you; for internal record keeping and administrative purposes; for analytics, market research and business development, including to operate and improve our website, associated applications and associated social media platforms; and to comply with our legal obligations and resolve any disputes that we may have.
4. Disclosure of personal information to third parties
We may disclose personal information to:
third party service providers for the purpose of enabling
them to provide their services, including (without limitation) IT service
providers, data storage, hosting and server providers, ad networks, analytics,
error loggers, debt collectors, maintenance or problem-solving providers,
marketing or advertising providers, professional advisors and payment systems
operators.
5. International transfers of personal information
The personal information we collect is stored and processed
in United Kingdom, or where we or our partners, affiliates and third-party
providers maintain facilities. By providing us with your personal information,
you consent to the disclosure to these overseas third parties.
We will ensure that any transfer of personal information
from countries in the European Economic Area (EEA) to countries outside the EEA
will be protected by appropriate safeguards, for example by using standard data
protection clauses approved by the European Commission, or the use of binding
corporate rules or other legally accepted means.
Where we transfer personal information from a non-EEA
country to another country, you acknowledge that third parties in other
jurisdictions may not be subject to similar data protection laws to the ones in
our jurisdiction. There are risks if any such third party engages in any act or
practice that would contravene the data privacy laws in our jurisdiction and
this might mean that you will not be able to seek redress under our
jurisdiction’s privacy laws.
6. Your rights and controlling your personal information
Choice and consent: By providing personal information to us, you consent to us collecting, holding, using and disclosing your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. If you are under 16 years of age, you must have and warrant to the extent permitted by law to us, that you have your parent or legal guardian’s permission to access and use the website and they (your parents or guardian) have consented to you providing us with your personal information. You do not have to provide personal information to us, however, if you do not, it may affect your use of this website or the products and/or services offered on or through it.
Information from third parties: If we receive personal
information about you from a third party, we will protect it as set out in this
privacy policy. If you are a third party providing personal information about
somebody else, you represent and warrant that you have such person’s consent to
provide the personal information to us.
Restrict: You may choose to restrict the collection or use
of your personal information. If you have previously agreed to us using your
personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at
any time by contacting us using the details below. If you ask us to restrict or
limit how we process your personal information, we will let you know how the
restriction affects your use of our website or products and services.
Access and data portability: You may request details of the
personal information that we hold about you. You may request a copy of the
personal information we hold about you. Where possible, we will provide this
information in CSV format or other easily readable machine format. You may
request that we erase the personal information we hold about you at any time.
You may also request that we transfer this personal information to another
third party.
Correction: If you believe that any information we hold
about you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading,
please contact us using the details below. We will take reasonable steps to
correct any information found to be inaccurate, incomplete, misleading or out
of date.
Notification of data breaches: We will comply with laws applicable to us in respect of any data breach.
Complaints: If you believe that we have breached a relevant
data protection law and wish to make a complaint, please contact us using the
details below and provide us with full details of the alleged breach. We will
promptly investigate your complaint and respond to you, in writing, setting out
the outcome of our investigation and the steps we will take to deal with your
complaint. You also have the right to contact a regulatory body or data
protection authority in relation to your complaint.
Unsubscribe: To unsubscribe from our e-mail database or
opt-out of communications (including marketing communications), please contact
us using the details below or opt-out using the opt-out facilities provided in
the communication.
7. Business transfers
If we or our assets are acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, we would include data among the assets transferred to any parties who acquire us. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that any parties who acquire us may continue to use your personal information according to this policy.
8. Limits of our policy
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated
by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and policies of
those sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective
privacy practices.
9. Changes to this policy
At our discretion, we may change our privacy policy to
reflect current acceptable practices. We will take reasonable steps to let
users know about changes via our website. Your continued use of this site after
any changes to this policy will be regarded as acceptance of our practices
around privacy and personal information.
If we make a significant change to this privacy policy, for
example changing a lawful basis on which we process your personal information,
we will ask you to re-consent to the amended privacy policy.
Lowther Loudspeaker SystemsLtd Data ControllerMartin Thorntoninfo@lowtherloudspeakers.com
Lowther Loudspeaker SystemsLtd Data Protection OfficerMartin Thorntoninfo@lowtherloudspeakers.com
This policy is effective as of 17 September 2019.
© 2020 Lowther Loudspeaker Systems Ltd   |   created by Rak Design
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Accept Read morePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Necessary
Always Enabled
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
